本字幕由YYeTs人人影視翻譯制作
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多字幕下載 請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
翻譯：路人z   冰藍藍   愛卿遛小鳥   魚小姐啦
翻譯：Michael  乖寶寶運氣好  小辮子  基恩的時間
時間軸：貝貝   愛卿遛小鳥   貓   校對：基恩的時間
后期：zzzyusa   總監：基恩的時間
幾個月前  我發現自己有一個孿生姐姐
A few months ago, I discovered I had a twin sister.
她要我去扮演她的角色
And then she she asked me to take her place,
保守秘密  尋找生母
keep the secret, find our real mother
努力保住性命
and try to stay alive.
如果你是我
Put yourself in my shoes.
這場謊言游戲你還能堅持多久
How long could you keep up the lying game?
我只是把一根撬胎棒
All I had to do was get a tire iron
放到瑞巴克先生的球包里
and drop it into Mr. Rybak's bag.
他陷害自己涉嫌謀殺嗎
Frame himself for murder?
他為何要這么做
Why would he do that?
擺脫我們的調查
To throw us off.
我就知道老爸是無辜的
I knew dad was innocent.
但是你從來不相信我
And you never listened
因為他不是你親生父親
because he's not your real father.
怎樣我們才能回到正軌
What will it take to make this right?
如果你現在向我保證
And if you were to promise me right now
你已經把一切都告訴我了
that you have told me everything.
我發誓我把一切都告訴了你
I swear you know everything.
我希望你能和克里斯汀重歸于好
I want you to work things out with Kristin.
我也很愿意陪在你身邊
And I'd like to be there for you.
我跟喬丹上過床
I hooked up with Jordan.
現在發現  他成了我新的繼哥哥
Now, it turns out he's my new stepbrother.
你真該考慮單飛
You should really think about going solo.
你拉琴的樣子真好看
It looks really good on you.
塞爾一直在我身邊
Thayer has always been there for me.
你和莎頓是天生一對
You and Sutton are perfect for each other.
所以你完全不介意
So, it's cool if Ethan and I give in
-我和伊森臣服于那顯露無疑的化學反應  -對
- to the chemistry between us? - Yeah.
你怎么才來
What took you so long?
見鬼
Aw, crap.
早上好  瞌睡蟲
Morning, sleepyhead.
老天  我干了什么
God, what did I do?
我呀
Me.
實際上  干了好幾次
Several times, actually.
不記得了嗎
Don't you remember?
當時我醉了
I was really drunk.
神志不清
Ow, I wasn't thinking.
我們都知道  我們考慮滾床單
Um, we both know we've been thinking
已經有一段時間了
about doing that for a while now.
這只是時間問題
It was only a matter of time.
我不該來這里
I never should've come here.
你在做什么  我還以為今天我們會一起度過
What are you doing? I thought we'd spend the day together.
我要去學校
I've got school.
但是昨晚你很爽  不是嗎
Well, you had a good time last night though, didn't you?
這不是重點
That's not the point, okay?
這是個錯誤  莎頓
It was a mistake, Sutton.
能把襯衫還給我嗎
Can I have my shirt back?
是因為艾瑪對嗎
This is because of Emma, isn't it?
對于這件事我真的很抱歉
I'm-I'm just really sorry about the whole thing, okay?
昨晚你看起來可沒什么歉意
Well, you didn't seem to be too sorry last night.
我知道  你是對的
I-I know... y-you're right.
你是對的  這對你不公平
You're right and that just was not fair to you.
我意識到了那點
I realize that and, um...
我保證不會再發生這事了
I promise it won't happen again.
《謊言游戲》  第二季第三集
你不該那么早就離開派對
You really shouldn't have left the party so early.
還有客人需要你接待
You still had guests to entertain.
比如說蘿倫·梅塞嗎
Like Laurel Mercer?
她只是你接近她爸爸所用的墊腳石
She's just a way for you to get closer to her dad.
大概吧  但我是你的話就會演下去
Maybe, but I'd play along if I were you.
如果你以前的一些過錯為人所知
'Cause it be a real shame
那將是真正的恥辱
if some of your past mistakes were to come to light.
不是嗎
Wouldn't it?
這樣吧  我們可以晚點討論這事
You know what? We can talk about this later.
你上學快遲到了
'Cause you're late for school.
我討厭你對我說教
I hate it when you get parental on me.
莎頓
Sutton?
我得和你說多少遍啊
How many times do I have to tell you?
抱歉  但這是緊急情況
I'm sorry, but this is an emergency.
我和伊森上床了
I slept with Ethan.
這不是什么緊急情況
That's not an emergency.
除非你沒有采取避孕措施
Unless, of course, you didn't use protection?
不  我采取了
No, I did.
今天早上他嚇壞了
He... he freaked out this morning.
他說他希望這一切沒有發生
And told me that he wished it didn't happen.
我很抱歉  莎頓
I'm so sorry, Sutton.
男孩有時就是這么殘酷
Boys can be so cruel.
這是她的錯
This is her fault.
如果我可以擺脫艾瑪  伊森就會忘了她
If I could just get rid of Emma, Ethan will forget about her.
她是你妹妹
She's your sister.
總有一天我們又會成為一家人
Someday we're going to be a family again.
你需要學會如何與她相處
And you need to get along with her.
他仍對她抱有幻想
He's holding out hope for her.
就像你爸爸一樣
Just like your father.
仍對克里斯汀抱有幻想
Holding out hope for Kristin.
是我在吐槽  你總能扯到自己身上去
Amazing how you can make my problems all about you.
事實是  你可以從我這里吸取教訓
The truth is, you could learn by my example.
我和泰德昨晚有過一段甜蜜時光
Ted and I kind of had a moment last night.
你行啊
Yay for you.
你也不錯
Yay for you too.
只要你聽我指揮
If you follow my lead.
我不會輕言放棄  你也不應該
I don't give up so easily, and neither should you.
好的  謝謝你的便車  兄弟
All right, thanks for the ride, man.
不客氣
No problem.
你昨晚去哪了
Where the hell you been all night?
和平常一樣  瞎玩
Screwing up like usual.
知道吧
You know?
我不得不搭便車
I had to hitch a ride.
說的太對了  你就是搞砸了
You're damn right you screwed up.
你老師打電話來了
Your teacher called.
比蒂老師嗎
Mr. Beattie?
你抄襲了一篇論文
You plagiarize a paper?
聽上去你已經知道了答案
Sounds like you already know the answer to that.
他把論文輸入了識別軟件
Yeah, he ran it through some software.
發現論文是網上購買的
Found out it was bought online.
丹  我知道我不該這樣做
Dan, I know I shouldn't have done that, okay?
省省吧  伊森
Save it, Ethan.
我不會讓你再回到少管所
I can't let you go back to juvie.
我讓比蒂給了你第二次機會
So I got Beattie to give you a second chance.
你去參加考試  范圍是這學期所有內容
You're going to take an exam on all the coursework.
很簡單  考試通過  就能結課
It's real simple: you pass the test, you pass the course.
好的  謝謝  什么時候考試
Okay, thanks. When is the test?
明天早上
Tomorrow morning.
就明天早上
It's tomorrow morning?
我怎么才能通過明天早上的考試
How am I going to pass a test tomorrow morning?
我不知道  你最好想想辦法
I don't know, but you better figure it out
因為你的未來取決于此
because your whole life depends on it.
警察局
你的眼睛怎么了
What happened to your eye?
我只是在交朋友
I'm just making friends.
監獄里人人都喜歡地方檢察官
Everybody in jail loves the D.A.
我就直說吧
Let me get this straight.
丹  我們的丹
Dan, our Dan,
居然覺得我是在陷害自己
came up with this crazy theory that I'm trying to frame myself?
這比你的解釋更為可信
You know it makes more sense than your own theory.
畢竟  是一個男人
After all, it was a man
打電話給女招待來陷害你
who called the waitress to set you up.
可能是麗貝卡干的
Rebecca could've done that.
她可能雇了別人
She could've hired someone.
或者  你自己打了電話
Or... you made the call yourself.
這件案子里  你應該代表我的利益
I thought you were trying to represent me here.
目的是把我弄出監獄
The objective was to get me out of jail.
你站在哪邊
Whose side are you on?
你雇我時告訴我
When you hired me, you told me
如果你能向我證明你的清白
that if you could convince me of your innocence,
陪審團也會相信你
you could convince a jury too. Well...
現在我沒那么相信你了
I'm not as convinced as I used to be.
查看女招待的電話記錄
Pull the waitress's phone records.
就能證明那通電話不是我打的
That'll prove I didn't make the call.
丹已經在查了
Dan's already on it.
今天下午就能知道結果
Should have them this afternoon.
特蕾莎
You know, Theresa,
你真的要把眼睛放亮點
you really ought to keep your eye on the ball.
麗貝卡才是幕后黑手
Rebecca's pulling the strings on this one.
不是我
Not me.
我聽到了陌生的手機鈴聲
I heard the strange ringtone
然后發現車庫里藏著這個
and I found this hidden in the garage.
-手機嗎  -對
- A cell phone? - Yeah.
警方不是已經搜查過你家了嗎
I thought the police already searched your whole house.
他們居然沒找到手機  這很奇怪
Well, I know, it's weird that they didn't find it,
但這肯定是爸爸的  我得上交
but it's got to be my dad's, so I have to turn it in.
等等  我們得查看一下他給誰打了電話
No, hold on, we need to check it and see who he called.
我已經看了
I already did.
所有來電都是無法查看
All incoming calls were blocked.
他撥打電話后就會清空記錄
And if he made any calls out, he cleared the log.
你能不能侵入手機  看看他刪掉了什么
Can't you hack into it and see what he deleted?
那可能被認為是篡改物證
But that might be considered tampering with evidence.
塞爾  要想查明他這段日子有什么企圖
Thayer, this is going to be our only way
這是唯一的辦法
we're gonna know what he's been up to all this time.
拜托  試試吧
Please? Can you just try?
好
Okay.
謝謝
Thank you.
不客氣
You're welcome.
他們好可愛哦
Aren't they adorable?
真不敢相信他們終于在一起了
I can't believe they finally got together.
她要進來了
She's coming.
自然點
Uh, act natural.
一切都好嗎
Hey, how's everything?
挺好的
Everything is fine.
你們是在監視我嗎
Were you spying on me?
我們嗎
Us?
沒有
No.
只是進來梳頭發
Just came in here to brush my hair.
用我的梳子嗎
With my brush?
好吧  我們是在監視你
Okay, we were totally spying.
天啊  你和塞爾  太棒了
Oh, my God. You and Thayer-- this is awesome.
你還真是"堅定"啊  蘿倫
Way to hold firm, Laurel.
小麥  你應該去和他談談
Mads, you should've come out and talked to him.
特別是昨晚的事發生以后
Especially after what happened last night.
他的嘴剛才正忙著呢
Well, his lips seemed pretty busy just now.
我還是回頭找他吧
So, I figured I'd do it later.
我不是想讓你們把注意力轉移到我身上
Okay, listen, not to make this all about me,
但我得問你們幾個問題
but I need to ask you guys a question.
你們覺得我約喬丹怎么樣
What do you think about me asking Jordan out?
好吧
Okay...
這主意糟透了
Terrible idea.
不是啦
No...
你有多了解他
How well do you know him?
怎么  你覺得我配不上他嗎
What? You think he's out of my league?
當然不是啦
No, of course not.
我只是覺得
I just think that...
我覺得你們很般配
I think you guys'd be great together.
你應該努力爭取  沒理由不這樣做
You should totally go for it. No reason not to.
太惡心了
This is disgusting!
這什么鬼東西
What is this?
天啊
God!
怎么了  你還好嗎
What's going on? Are you okay?
水槽堵了
Well, the sink is clogged.
也許爸爸能搞定
Ew, well, maybe Dad could fix it.
不  我現在不想依靠他
No, I don't want to have to rely on him right now.
我能自己搞定
I can take care of this myself.
我還以為心理治療挺順利
But I thought therapy went well.
那不意味著我們會重歸于好
That doesn't mean we are getting back together.
你試過污物碾碎器嗎
Have you tried the disposal?
也許會有用
Maybe that'll clear it?
這主意真好
That is a very good idea.
瞧瞧  姑娘們
You see, girls?
我們能自己搞定
We can handle this ourselves.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我去打電話給水管工
Um, I'll call a plumber.
阿羅約高中
哥們
Dude.
你和莎頓·梅塞和好了
You and Sutton Mercer back together again, huh?
我送你去小木屋時好像看到了她
Look, I might've seen her when I dropped you at the cabin.
她跑得真快
I mean, that girl moves fast.
我們沒發生什么
Nothing happened, okay?
不  真的很快
No, like literally fast.
像閃電俠一樣
Like The Flash.
開始她還在派對上
You know, she was at the party one minute,
接著就去了小木屋
then the cabin the next.
她肯定是抄了近路
She must've taken a shortcut.
她快馬加鞭趕去那里和你秘密約會
So, she races down there for a secret rendezvous,
你們居然沒有上床
and you guys don't even hook up?
你不會以為我會信你吧
Come on, you don't really expect me to believe that, do you?
喬丹  管好自己的嘴
Jordan, you need to keep your mouth shut.
行嗎
All right?
你什么都沒看見
You didn't see anything.
知道了嗎
Got it?
知道了
Got it.
她沒在那里
She wasn't there.
她也肯定不在大廳里
And she's definitely not down the hall either.
姑娘們好
Ladies.
他肯定是在看你
He was totally checking you out.
惡心  他是我繼哥哥
Ew, he's my stepbrother.
盡管如此  你得告訴蘿倫
Regardless, you have to tell Laurel
你和他上床了
that you hooked up with him.
今早你聽到她的話了
You heard her this morning.
她在說要約他出來
She was talking about asking him out.
那只不過是毫無意義的一夜情
It was a meaningless one-time thing,
我們約好對此絕口不提
and we've agreed never to speak about it again.
就像沒發生過一樣
It's like it didn't even happen.
但確實發生了
But it did happen.
我生物課要遲到了
I'm late for Bio.
大掃除呢
Cleaning out?
事實上  是退學
Dropping out, actually.
比蒂查出
Beattie found out
我那份世界文明史的論文是剽竊來的
I plagiarized that World Civ paper.
現在我也成了歷史
So, now I'm history.
不過也跟你沒關系
Not that it's any your business.
你會回少管所嗎
Well, won't you go back to juvie?
也許那里才是我的歸宿
Well, maybe that's where I belong.
不  伊森  一定有辦法的
No, Ethan, there has to be something you can do.
我明天必須過一場考試
Yeah, there's a test I'd have to pass tomorrow
內容涵蓋整學期的課程
on all the course material,
但我過不了  因為我落下太多了
but I can't do that because I'm too far behind,
所以我一開始才會作弊
which is why I cheated in the first place.
等等
Wait.
干什么
What?
我教你
I'll tutor you.
你為什么還在乎
Why do you even care?
在我做了那些事之后
After everything I did.
你不是跟塞爾在一起了嗎
Aren't you with Thayer now?
拜托  這跟他沒關系
Oh, come on. This has nothing to do with him.
事關你的將來
This is about your future.
你不能就此放棄
You can't just give up.
讓我幫你吧
Please, just let me help you.
以后再說
Later.
抱歉
Excuse me.
我幫你吧
Let me help.
天哪  我真是笨手笨腳
Oh, my gosh, I'm such a klutz.
也許他們應該在書上貼警示標記
Maybe they should put warning labels on these things.
你真幽默
You're hilarious.
是這樣的
Um, hey, look,
我知道這么說有點倉促
I know this is really short notice, um,
比特·巴倫今晚在十九號飛機庫打碟
but DJ Beat Baron is spinning tonight at Hangar 19.
我準備去的
And I was thinking of going.
你要來嗎
Would you want to come?
我都不知道比特·巴倫來鎮上了
I didn't even know that Beat Baron was in town.
他的混音超贊的
His mixes are so sick.
那你會來
So, you in?
當然
Yeah, for sure.
七點去接你
Um, pick up around 7:00?
說定了
It's a date.
我是說  定下這個時間[date有約會之意]
I mean, a date in the calendar sense of the word.
好的
Right.
那到時見
All right, I'll see you then.
好的
Okay.
小麥  我記得你說要道歉
Mads, I thought you said you wanted to apologize.
我在道歉呢
I am apologizing.
為昨晚的事  但我還是堅信爸爸無罪
For last night, but not for thinking Dad's innocent.
我告訴過你  他說
I told you, he said...
我才不管他說過什么
I don't care what he said.
他玩弄你  正如他玩弄全世界
He's playing you just like he plays everyone.
孩子們
Guys?
沒事吧
Everything okay?
沒事
Yeah, fine.
不  有事
No, it's not fine.
麗貝卡  告訴他
Rebecca, tell him about the fingerprint
警方在高爾夫球袋上找到他人指紋
they found on the golf bag.
從而證明  爸爸是遭人陷害的
They can prove that Dad's been set up,
爸爸從一開始就是這么說的
just like he's been saying all along.
我不想讓你們充滿期待
Well, I didn't want to get anybody's hopes up,
不過事情的確出現了轉機
but things are looking a lot better now.
我不會現在就開香檳慶祝
Well, I wouldn't pop that champagne just yet.
失陪了  我還有事要做
Excuse me, guys. I have work to do.
等等  我們還沒說完呢
Wait. We weren't finished talking.
塞爾  留下吧
Thayer, stay.
不如我們今晚一起吃晚餐吧
Why don't we all go to dinner together?
我請客
My treat.
我和莎頓今晚要打網球
Sutton and I are playing tennis tonight.
她馬上要參加地區賽了  抱歉
She has Regionals coming up. Sorry.
回見
See you.
他就是不聽勸
He just won't listen.
他會明白的
Oh, he'll come around.
小麥  我真正擔心的是你
Mads, it's you that I'm actually worried about.
你爸爸身陷囹圄  你住在梅塞家
Between all of this, your dad being in jail,
他們倆夫妻還在鬧離婚  這么多事
living at the Mercers while they're going through divorce.
泰德和克里斯汀在做心理治療
Well, Ted and Kristin are actually in therapy now.
關系有所改善了
So, things seem better.
是嗎
Really?
是的
Yeah.
那太好了
That's so good to hear.
太好了  你來了
Oh, good, you made it.
我沒想到你會來這么
I didn't think you would get here so...
等一下
Wait a second.
我特別關照孩子們別給你打電話
I told the girls specifically not to call you.
是嗎  蘿倫說得好像
Really? 'Cause Laurel made it sound
你都在求我過來了
like you were practically begging me to come over.
下水道也是她們堵的吧
Did they clog the drain too?
是她們干的也不出奇  我們家的孩子嘛
Wouldn't put it past them-- our girls.
真是詭計多端
Pretty crafty.
這是什么
Aww, what is this?
羊排  魚  雞肉
Lamb chops, some kind of fish, chicken.
想做什么  香溜肉片嗎
What are you thinking, piccata?
帕爾馬干酪肉片
Parmigiana.
真想吃家里的飯啊
Kill for a home-cooked meal,
不過我可沒在暗示什么
not that I'm hinting at anything.
你不覺得這事為時尚早嗎
Don't you think it's a little early for that?
是的
Right.
說到這個  我今天跟桑迪醫生通過電話
Speaking of which, I spoke to Dr. Sandy's office.
她說她周一早上十點有空
She said she has a time for us Monday at 10:00?
我有約了
I actually have another appointment at that time.
我也不想
And I'm not...
我不太想取消
I'm not sure that I want to cancel it, so...
不要有壓力  沒事的
No pressure, that's fine.
告訴我一聲就行
Just let me know.
我得去借個疏通工具
I have to rent a rooter for this,
-能等我明天弄嗎  -當然
- so can you wait till tomorrow? - Sure.
打給杰西卡·惠特曼的電話
The call to Jessica Whitman
是從一次性手機撥出的
was made from a burner cell,
有可能手機現在已經銷毀了
so chances are it's been destroyed by now.
也就是說  誰都有可能打給她
In other words, anyone could've called her,
包括埃里克
including Alec.
所以我給他秘書打了電話
Which is why I called his secretary
問問他那天的行程
to check his schedule that day.
從你這副表情看來  我猜你有所發現
And from that look, I'm guessing you found something.
他提早走了
He took off early.
一整個下午都不在  也沒說去哪
Was gone all afternoon. Didn't say where.
有點意思
Huh, that's interesting.
是的
Yeah.
非常抱歉  網球練習
I'm so sorry. I have to
我去不了了  有點事
bail on you for tennis. Something came up.
不論何事  都要靠邊站
Well, whatever it is, it should wait
因為我查到我爸用那部手機打給誰了
because I found out who my dad called with that cell phone.
他打給了杰西卡·惠特曼
Apparently, he made one call to a Jessica Whitman.
號碼已經聯系不上了
Number's been disconnected,
但我覺得我們可以共同努力
but I figured we could work together
把她找出來
and try and find her.
我今晚沒空
I can't tonight.
但是...
But...
但是沒我你也能搞定
But you can do it without me.
我晚點打給你  好嗎
I'll call you later, okay?
等等  他們現在和好了嗎
Wait, they're getting along now?
我還以為他們彼此仇視呢
I thought they hated each other.
那是"七年戰爭"時候
That was during the Seven Years' War.
1756~1763年  英法普奧俄等國在歐洲 北美 印度等地進行爭奪殖民地戰爭
一戰的時英法兩國結成同盟
During World War I, France and England were allies.
如果他們都搞不明白誰喜歡誰
Well, how am I supposed to keep this stuff straight
我怎么能把這些事記清楚呢
if even they can't decide who likes who?
這比高中生糾葛還復雜
This is worse than high school.
或許你專心點別玩球就能記住
Maybe if you just focus and put the ball down.
我很專心啊
I am focused.
真的
I really am.
但是我專心思考的是
But I am focusing on how this is going
這究竟是多么浪費生命的事啊
to be a huge waste of my time.
你說得對
You're right.
你不想學  我怎么教都沒用
I can't teach you if you don't want to learn.
祝你在少管所玩得愉快
So have fun in juvie.
好吧  等等  等一下嘛
All right, wait, wait. Hang on a second, okay?
我就是覺得我不值得
I just feel like I don't deserve this.
什么
What?
你的幫助
Your help.
好吧
Okay.
你犯了個錯  伊森
You made a mistake, Ethan.
而你現在有機會改正
And now you have a chance to make it right.
伊森  我相信你
Ethan, I believe in you.
艾瑪  有件事我得告訴你
Emma, I have to tell you something.
我...
I...
希望我沒打攪你們
Well, hope I'm not interrupting anything.
莎頓  你瘋了嗎
Sutton, are you crazy?
你能不能放輕松點
Oh, would you relax?
我查過丹現在還在上班
I checked to make sure Dan was still at work.
我過來看看
I was stopping by
伊森要不要和我共進晚餐
to see if Ethan wanted to join me for dinner,
但顯然  他已經有安排了
but, apparently, he has plans.
不是你想的那樣  好嗎
It's not what you think, all right?
我  我明天有個考試
I've-I've got a test tomorrow.
我們  我們在學習  她在輔導我
We're... we're studying. She's helping me.
真是貼心啊
Oh, well, that's really sweet.
我批準了
I approve.
認真的嗎
Seriously?
那當然  我們都不希望小情人
Yes, seriously, we don't want lover boy
最后又回到少管所  對吧
to end up back in juvie now, do we?
小情人
Lover boy?
拜托  就是打個比方而已
Oh, come on. It's a figure of speech.
我們真有好多內容要復習
We really have a lot of work to do right now.
好的  那我把這些留在這兒
Okay, well, then I will leave you these.
當做一會兒餓了的點心
Just for a little snack, for later.
你最喜歡的那家燒烤店買的
It's from that favorite barbeque place you like.
祝你明天好運
Good luck tomorrow.
他不用碰運氣
He doesn't need luck.
他有我呢
He has me.
你該看看她那嘴臉
You should have seen her.
裝得一副天真無辜的樣子
Playing all innocent.
如果我還待在那兒沒走
I'm telling you that if I would have stayed there,
因謀殺入獄的就不只埃里克一個了
Alec wouldn't be the only one in jail for murder.
我接下來要說的話
You're going to be a lot happier
會讓你開心許多的
after you hear what I have to say.
什么話能讓我好過點
What could you possibly say that would make me feel better?
我想要你...
I want you...
把原來的生活從艾瑪手中奪過來
to take your life back from Emma.
什么時候換回身份也在計劃之中了
Since when is switching back ever been part of the plan?
我也只能這么做
It's just there's only so much I can do
防止泰德和克里斯汀和好了
to keep Ted and Kristin apart.
你要我從內部瓦解他倆的感情
So, you want me to work from the inside to split them up?
換個角度想
Well, think about it this way:
艾瑪要被孤立在此
Emma will be here in isolation,
而你能重出江湖
while you're out and about,
也就是說  沒人和你爭伊森了
which means you'll have Ethan all to yourself.
要知道她可不樂意這么做
You know she's not going to do this willingly.
你得找個法子勸服她
Mmm, you're going to have to find a way to persuade her.
別讓我失望啊  小甜心
Don't let me down, pumpkin.
小麥
Mads.
我沒走錯吧
Am I at the right house?
我就是在這兒住一陣子
Yeah, I'm just staying here for a little bit.
進來吧
Come on in.
蘿倫很快就好了
Laurel, uh, should be ready in a minute.
抱歉  我不知道你在這兒
Sorry, I didn't realize you'd be here.
有點尷尬
Guess this is kind of awkward.
有什么可尷尬的
Why would it be awkward?
明白了
Gotcha.
好了  多謝你招待他
All set. Thanks for entertaining him.
沒問題  你們倆好好玩
Yeah, not a problem. You two have fun.
你想來嗎
Hey, do you want to come?
我不行
Uh, I can't.
我可不想打擾你們
I don't want to impose.
開什么玩笑  我們就是出去玩
Are you kidding? We're just hanging out.
但我以為...
But I thought...
你也來吧
No, you should come.
又不是約會什么的
It's not like it's a date or anything.
喬丹  你能讓我們講兩句嗎
Jordan, can you give us a sec?
這回你必須跟我們走
Okay, now you have to come with us.
不行  我沒心情
No, I'm so not in the mood.
是你讓我約他出來的
You were the one who told me to ask him out,
現在我徹底是當局者迷
and now I'm totally confused.
如果你一塊兒來  還能幫我
If you come along, you can help me figure out
看看他是不是真的喜歡我
whether or not he's really into me or not.
拜托了
Please?
好吧
Fine.
先說好...
For the record...
她也去  我們出發吧
She's in. Let's roll.
一字都不許提
Not a word.
打電話給杰西卡·惠特曼那天
You left work early the day
你提早下班了
that call to Jessica Whitman was made.
唯一使我愧疚的就是
The only thing I'm guilty of is
為了打高爾夫提早下班
leaving work early to play some golf.
你發表長篇大論之前
And before you say anything,
先搞明白高爾夫球場是不能用手機的
you're not allowed to have cell phones on the golf course, okay?
下周你得把我弄出去
We should get out next week.
你覺得呢  有空嗎
What do you say? You free?
她有空  你沒空
She is. You aren't.
三思啊  丹尼
Oh, think again, Danny Boy.
我可是有證人支持的
I've got a witness that'll back me up.
你們倆
You two
剛給了我那張無罪釋放的王牌
just gave me a get-out-of-jail-free card.
你好啊  妹妹
Hey, sis.
你在外面玩到好晚啊
You were out late.
你嚇死我了  莎頓
Oh, you scared the crap out of me, Sutton.
你真的應該時不時地
Hey, you know, you should really get
把球拍的網緊一緊
these re-strung every now and then.
你這是想要干嘛
What do you think you're doing?
你是不能去打網球的
You can't go play tennis.
你應該避開大家的視線
You're supposed to be staying out of sight.
而你應該為地區賽賽多加練習
And you're supposed to be practicing for Regionals,
不過這也沒妨礙你
but that doesn't seem to stop you
去伊森那兒幫他補習
from going over to Ethan's and tutoring him.
我知道你對那件事有些生氣
I knew you were upset about that.
我沒有生氣
Oh, I'm not upset.
我很高興你能幫他
I'm thrilled that you're helping him.
我只是不想輸掉地區賽
I just don't want to lose Regionals either.
你知道的  這場比賽關系重大
You know, a lot is riding on it:
參加大學甲級賽   拿獎學金
a chance to play D-1 tennis,
可全靠它了
and scholarship.
你什么時候開始關心這些了
Since when has any of that mattered to you?
我在小屋有大把的時間可以思考這些
Since I had a lot of time to think up at that cabin.
而且現實是
And the fact of the matter is,
我們倆將來都要去上大學
you and I are both going to have to go to college someday.
不用擔心  我已經準備好了參加比賽
Well, don't worry. I'm ready for the tournament.
而且我也會贏到獎學金
And I'm gonna win the scholarship.
我知道  但是多練一下也無妨
Yeah, but a little bit of practice wouldn't hurt.
所以我就在想  我可以指點你一下
So, I was thinking, I can just give you some pointers.
就明天吧
We go out tomorrow.
就當是玩了
Just for fun.
會被人看見的  莎頓
Someone will see us, Sutton.
那我們就到小鎮外面
Then, we'll do it across town.
這樣就沒人能認出我們了
No one will recognize us.
多大點事
What is the big deal?
你為什么這么執著呢
Why is this so important to you?
天啊  我只是想跟我的妹妹
Geez, just thought I'd spend
享受一下美好時光
some quality time with my sister,
不過你要是沒興趣的話
but if you're not interested.
不是的
No.
實際上我愿意去
Actually, I would love to.
說定了  姐姐
You're on, sis.
很感謝你能來
Thanks for coming down.
實際上我也正準備跟你談談
Actually, I was already planning on talking to you.
談什么
About what?
你先說吧  你不說這事很重要嗎
Well, you first. You said it was important.
我們需要你做一份聲明
Well, we need you to make a statement.
我們又發現了一些新證據
Some new evidence has come to light.
有人給那家俱樂部的女服務生打了個電話
Someone called a waitress at the club
花錢讓她去把那根撬胎棒
and paid her to plant the tire iron
放到你爸的高爾夫球袋里
in your father's golf bag.
-等一下 有人打過電話  -是的
- Wait. Somebody called? - Yeah.
那個女服務生的名字叫什么
What was the waitress's name?
杰西卡·惠特曼
Jessica Whitman.
給她打電話的那個人陷害了你爸  塞爾
Whoever called her set your father up, Thayer.
我的天啊  丹  他不是被陷害的
Oh, my God. Dan, he wasn't set up.
他就是打電話的那個人
He's the one who called.
你好  小塞
Hello, T.
-這是什么意思  -沒關系的  塞爾
- What the hell?  - It's okay, Thayer.
我們只是需要問你幾個問題
We just need to ask you some questions.
我也正好有幾個問題
Well, I've got some questions of my own.
比如說
Like....
你怎么解釋這個東西呢
How do you explain this, for example?
老爸
Dad?
你怎么能說你之前沒見過這部手機呢
How can you say you've never see that phone before?
我是在家里發現的
I found it in our house.
如果這部手機一直在咱們家里
If it was there the whole time,
那么警察搜查的時候為什么沒有發現它呢
why didn't the police find it when the searched the house?
肯定是他們疏忽了
They must have missed it.
得了吧  聽我說  無論是誰放在那的
Come on. Look, whoever planted the phone there,
肯定是在警察搜查過之后放的
planted it there after the search.
他們給這部手機打電話
And then they called it
就是要讓你發現它
to be sure you'd find it.
又或者可能是你玩砸了
Or maybe you just screwed up.
你以為藏得很好  實則不然
And you didn't hide it as well as you think you did.
我不是傻子  兒子
I'm no fool, son.
但你是個殺人犯
But you're a murderer.
好了  別再說了
Okay, that's enough.
這對我們一點幫助都沒有
This isn't getting us anywhere.
檢測結果出來了
I got the lab results.
我們的技術人員證實了
Our techs confirmed that...
確實是有人用這部電話
it is indeed the cell phone used
打給了杰西卡·惠特曼
to call Jessica Whitman.
真不幸啊
Ouch.
結案了
Case closed.
他們還證實了
They also determined
打給杰西卡的那通電話
that the call to Jessica...
是從亞利桑那州的旗桿市打出的
was made from Flagstaff, Arizona.
打那通電話的時刻
Weren't we playing golf the exact time
不正是我們玩高爾夫的時候嗎
that phone call was made?
是個星期五  對吧
Yeah, it was a Friday, right?
我能記得是因為你贏了我一桿
I remember it 'cause you beat me by one.
你打了個小鳥球[比標準桿少一桿進洞]
You birdied 18.
我知道  我記得
I know. I remember.
那么我是如何做到既在斯科茨代爾市
So how could I be playing golf with you in Scottsdale,
跟你打跟你打高爾夫  又出現在
and also be in Flagstaff,
150英里之外的旗桿市的呢
150 miles away?
我怎么知道  或許你雇了某個人
I don't know. Maybe you hired someone.
又或許有兩個我
Or maybe there's two of me.
太意想不到了
Well, it backfired.
現在我們已經有了足夠的證據
'Cause we got enough to go to the judge
讓法官取消對你的一切指控
and get the charges against you dropped.
我的天啊  不不不  請不要
Oh, my God. No, no, no, please, please,
-你不能讓他出去  -小塞  接受吧
- You can't let him out. - T, face it...
你看錯了所有的事情
You were wrong about everything,
而我唯一做錯的是
and the only mistake I made
在當初沒人可憐你時
was taking your bastard ass in
撿回了你這個白眼狼
when nobodelse gave a crap about you.
住手  住手
Hey, hey, hey! Okay, okay...
我們走  我們走
Let's go. Let's go.
我們走
Let's go.
該死的  他現在不能被放出來
Damn it. This can't be happening right now.
無論你愿不愿意  你爸都會被釋放
You dad's getting out whether you like it or not.
你得接受這個現實
You need to find a way to deal with that.
現在回家去  冷靜一下
Now go home and cool off.
您好  我是林賽·里奇韋律師辦公室的
Hi, this is Lindsey Ridgeway's office
我想提醒您別忘了周一上午10點的預約
reminding you of your appointment for Monday 10:00 A.M.
請回復我以便確認
Please call us back to confirm.
你還是要去見你的離婚事務律師嗎
You're still going to meet with your divorce attorney?
還不確定
I don't know.
可能吧
Maybe.
我們碰巧在那個時候有一次心里咨詢
It turns out we have a therapy session
在同一時間  所以我必須取消一個
the exact same time, so I do have to cancel one of them.
我能投票選哪個嗎
Do I get a vote on which one?
我已經知道你想選哪個了  謝謝你
Oh, I already know your vote, thank you very much,
別以為我不知道你們幾個女孩
and don't think I don't know what you girls were up to
在水管那事上搞什么鬼
with the whole plumbing thing. You are not
你們沒自己想得那么聰明
as clever as you think you are.
重點是  我們會不擇手段
The point is, we would do anything
維護家庭的完整
to keep this family intact.
取消和離婚律師的會面
And cancelling on the divorce attorney
一點不過火
is hardly going to extremes.
我喜歡這地方
I like this place.
你呢  小麥
What do you think, Mads?
我覺得好多人
I think there's too many people
太過努力地故作鎮定
trying too hard to be cool,
不過我倒不驚訝你喜歡這里
but I'm not surprised you like it.
什么情況
Excuse me?
她開玩笑呢
She's just kidding.
你開玩笑呢  是吧
You were just kidding, right?
是啊  你懂的  蘿倫
Yes, and you would know, Laurel,
因為你有極好的幽默感
because you have an amazing sense of humor,
有感染力的笑容
an infectious laugh,
超級棒的人品
great personality...
-得了吧  -有人會覺得她才貌兼備
- Stop. - Some might say that she is the total package.
別妄自菲薄
Well, don't sell yourself short.
謝謝你  繼兄
Ugh. Well, thank you, stepbrother.
我要去吧臺
I'm gonna go to the bar.
有人要喝酒嗎
Anyone want a drink?
當然  要我幫你嗎
Sure. You want any help?
不用  你陪蘿倫  我去買酒
No. You stay here with Laurel. I'll get the drinks.
至少讓我付錢吧
Well, at least let me buy.
我真的不要你的錢
I really don't want your money.
不好意思
Hey, I'm sorry.
我做錯什么了嗎
Did I do something wrong?
她又來了
Ha! There she goes again.
我喝水就行
Hey, I'll just take a water.
沒問題吧
If that's cool.
你喝什么  小麥
What're you gonna drink, Mads?
四海為家  還是激情海岸
A Cosmo? Sex on the beach?
我要回家
You know what? I'm gonna go home.
他歸你一個人了  你們倆
He's all yours. You two
玩得開心點
enjoy your evening.
我真覺得很抱歉
Um, I'm really sorry.
我不知道怎么了
I have no idea what just happened.
別管它了
Forget about it.
沒事的
It's fine.
我們跳舞吧
Let's dance.
好
Yeah.
謝謝
Thanks.
今天來打球
You playing today?
不是  我熱熱身
No, I was just warming up.
我要出城跟莎頓比賽
I'm actually headed across town to have a match with Sutton.
-真的嗎  -嗯  她的主意
- Seriously? Mm-hmm. - It was her idea.
我肯定她另有所圖
I'm sure she has some sort of ulterior motive.
就你們倆嗎
You guys are gonna just be alone together?
是啊  就我們倆
Yes, we're gonna be alone together.
我迫不及待知道她在想什么
I can't wait to hear what she has on her mind.
你的考試怎么樣了
How did your test go?
Uh, 73.
我過了
I passed.
-太棒了  -是啊  因為
- That's awesome. - Yeah, well,
我的補習老師很棒
I had a pretty good tutor.
你還想接著幫我嗎
You think you might want to keep helping me with that stuff?
我就能繼續自由自在了
So I can stay a freeman.
可以啊  好啊
Yeah, I can do that. Yeah.
好的  謝謝
All right. Thanks.
過來
Come here.
真替你高興
I'm so happy for you.
怎么了這是
What's going on here?
我正感謝她幫我呢
Um, I was just thanking her for helping me.
她給我補習
Uh, she tutored me.
給你補習
Tutoring you?
對  我以為你知道的
Yeah. I thought you knew.
真心不知道
Uh, no, actually.
等等  所以昨晚
Wait, hold on. So last night...
你必須去做的就是這個嗎
that's where you had to go?
考試就在今天
The test was today.
那我只能說  無所謂
You know what? It doesn't matter.
塞爾
Thayer...
埃里克今天放出來嗎
Alec's getting out?
法官正簽字呢
The judge is signing it up right now.
顯然他是被陷害的
He's obviously been framed.
當然了  誰陷害的
Of course. By whom?
懷疑是亞利桑那州旗桿市的一個女服務生
Well, the call to the waitress came from Flagstaff, Arizona.
有印象嗎
Does that mean anything to you?
旗桿市  沒有
Flagstaff, uh, no.
一點都沒有
Not at all.
不管怎樣  今晚之前他就能出來了
Anyway, he should be out by this evening.
你們好好慶祝吧
You two should celebrate.
會的  我還以為永遠都等不到今天了呢
Yes, I thought this day would never come.
謝謝你  特蕾莎
Thank you so much, Theresa.
泰德  我剛剛得知
Hey, Ted, I just got
-一個極好的消息  -是嗎  什么
- the most amazing news. - Really? What?
埃里克被放出來了
Alec's being released.
-真的嗎  -是啊
- Really? - Yeah.
那
Wow. That...
真出人意料
I didn't expect that.
我也沒想到
Neither was I.
說實在的
Actually.
為什么你這么沮喪
Well why are you so upset?
我很害怕  泰德
I'm scared, Ted.
每次我去監獄探望埃里克
It's just whenever I've gone to see
都會覺得
Alec in jail, I've gotten the feeling
他也許在將被捕的事怪罪于我
that he might blame me for his arrest.
怎么可能
Well, that's ridiculous.
你比任何人都支持他
You've been more supportive than anyone.
是倒是  不過
Yeah, well...
你知道他的
you know how he gets.
他的暴脾氣
His temper.
如果你那么害怕的話
Well, if you are that afraid,
干脆出城好了
why don't you leave town?
回洛杉磯吧
Go back to L.A.?
你不是說真的吧
You don't really mean that?
我還以為
I thought that...
你想多了
You thought wrong.
懂了
I see.
我不能
Well, I can't...
再逃跑一次
run away, not again.
我是說  我深愛的一切都在這
I mean, everything I love is here.
我的根
My roots are here.
我的家人都在這
My family is here.
你是說喬丹
You mean Jordan?
我還能說誰
Who else would I mean?
好吧  見諒
Well, I'm, I'm sorry.
我不該在你面前這么失態
I shouldn't have fallen apart on you like this.
謝謝你陪我
And I thank you for being there for me.
再見
see you.
我是塞爾  請留言
This is Thayer, you know what to do.
塞爾  還是我  艾瑪
Thayer, hi. It's Emma again.
你還好嗎
Are you okay?
給我回電話吧
Please call me back.
為愛傷神嗎
Trouble in paradise?
你確信這里沒人能認出我們
Are you sure nobody's gonna recognize us here?
拜托  知道的人都會被滅口的
Please, anyone worth knowing would be caught dead here.
好吧
All right.
你開球
You serve.
看來你是很久沒練習了
I'm sure you haven't played in a while.
艾瑪  你總是很體貼
Always so considerate, Emma.
想把事情變得有趣些嗎
Well, care to make things interesting?
你想干什么
Well, what did you have in mind?
贏的人當然是最佳運動員
Well, whoever wins is obviously the best player,
打地區賽的就應該是最佳運動員
so she should be the one that plays at Regionals.
原來是為這個
So that's what this is about.
你想換回來了
You want to switch back.
就幾天  為了地區賽
For a few days. Just for Regionals.
除非  你害怕了
Unless, of course, you're too scared, then...
但那沒必要
you don't have to.
我才沒有  你才該害怕
Oh, I'm not scared. You should be scared,
因為我會跟你死拼
'cause I will wipe these courts with you.
沖勁十足啊  艾瑪
Feisty, Emma.
好  我們說定了
Fine. We have a deal?
還沒  我也有條件
No, actually, I have some of my own terms.
輸的人  得待在小木屋里
Whoever loses...has to stay in the cabin.
這次是真格的
For real this time.
不許邁出一步  明白嗎
Can't step foot out of it. Understand?
說定了  祝你好運
Deal. Good luck.
祝我的好妹妹贏
May the best sister win.
我會的
Oh, I will.
你好
Oh, hey.
我想向你道歉
I wanted to apologize
為昨晚的事
for last night. I, um,
-我是不是把事情搞砸了  -才不是
- I guess I kind of screwed things up. Oh, no.
你的離開再好不過了
Leaving was the best thing you could've done.
一開始就不該叫你一起去的
I never should've asked you to come along.
你和喬丹一切都好
Oh, so things worked out with you and Jordan?
我們跳了一會舞  聊了好久
We danced for a while and talked for, like, hours
聊音樂啊  樂隊啊  還有生活
about music and bands and life.
他很可愛
He's so sweet and cute.
我想我們下周還會約會的
I think we're gonna go out again next week.
太好了  真為你們高興
Awesome. Well, I'm really happy for you.
我也是
Me, too.
你真好
You're the best.
塞爾  怎么了
Hey, Thayer. What's up?
什么
What?
第一輪我6比2勝出
That's me on the first set. 6-2.
你還真不賴
You're on fire.
如果你愿意我們可以不打了
Well, we can quit if you want.
不用  我就是有點不在狀態
No, no. I'm just a little off.
這禮拜都沒怎么睡好
Haven't really been getting much sleep this week.
因為你滿城跑
That's 'cause you're running around town
而你本該在小木屋老實待著休息
when you should be up at that cabin just relaxing.
很難有空休息
Yeah, well, it's kind of hard to relax
伊森會在半夜跑來
when Ethan just drops by in the middle of the night.
抱歉
Excuse me.
喬丹的派對后  他來過
after Jordan's party, he stopped by,
你說沒關系  我們就做愛了
and you said it was fine, so I slept with him.
你不會生氣吧
You're cool with that, right?
沒有  他
Yeah, whatever. He can...
他想怎樣就怎樣吧
He can do what he wants.
那就好  我還以為你會難過呢
Good, 'cause I totally thought you'd be, like, really upset.
我沒有
I'm not.
看得出來
Obviously.
該我開球了
My serve.
貌似那個  那個
The, um, the cam, um...
緊鏈器
Chain tensioner.
對  就是那個
Yeah, that's the one.
有噪音
make noises.
能幫忙看看嗎
Do you mind taking It's makinga look at it?
好的
All right.
莎頓不在這吧
Sutton's not here, is she?
她為什么要在這
Why would she be?
隨口問問
Just asking.
從來都不知道她會突然在哪冒出來
Never seem to know where she's gonna pop up next.
好像不是緊鏈器的問題
It didn't sound like your tensioner, but, um,
我們得檢查一下你的火花塞
we're probably gonna check your plugs out, all right?
你們之間到底有什么事
What's the deal with you guys anyways?
聽著  這很復雜
Look, it's, uh... it's complicated.
她過去是一個人  現在成了另一個人
Okay, she used to be one person and...now she's someone else.
而你卻不清楚自己更喜歡哪個
And you don't know which one you like more.
-就是那樣  -妞們都這樣
- Something like that, yeah. - Chicks.
即使你知道她們對你來說完全不可能
Even when you know they're completely wrong for you,
還是忍不住想她們
you still can't stop thinking about them.
聽起來你才是有問題的那個啊
Sounds to me like you're the one with the problem.
可不是嗎
Yeah, tell me about it.
不過  我確實在木屋里見過莎頓
But hey, I did see Sutton at the cabin.
她真的很喜歡你
She's into you, man.
全身心的愛你呢
Like, hardcore into you.
我要是你
If I were you,
才不會想那么多
I wouldn't overthink it.
我要是你
If I were you,
我也不會
I wouldn't either.
艾瑪
Emma!
小麥
Mads?
暫停一下
Time-out.
謝天謝地找到你了
Thank God I found you.
怎么了
What's the matter?
塞爾打電話來告別
Thayer just called to say good-bye.
他要回洛杉磯了
He's moving back to L.A.
我想他和我爸可能鬧得很兇
I guess things got pretty ugly between him and my dad.
我就知道他有事
Oh, I knew something was wrong with him.
糟糕  有好戲看了
Uh-oh. Drama.
我很想從中和解
I really wanted to make peace between them,
但他根本聽不進去
but he won't listen to me,
艾瑪  我覺得
and Emma, I think you might be
你是唯一一個能讓他留下的人
the only person who can keep him here.
你動作得快
And you've got to hurry
因為他已經在收拾行囊了
'cause he's packing right now.
分秒必爭
Tick-tock.
恭喜你  莎頓
Congratulations, Sutton.
你贏了  我認輸
You win. I forfeit.
塞爾
Thayer.
你不該來的  艾瑪
You shouldn't have come, Emma.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你和埃里克怎么了
What happened with Alec?
他贏了  一如往常
He won, like he always does.
他馬上就出獄  所以我沒法繼續留在這
He's getting out of jail, so I can't stay here anymore.
什么  他要出獄了
What, he's getting out?
怎么回事
How?
我找到的那部手機反而使他免罪
That phone I found exonerated him.
你能相信么
Can you believe that?
好吧
Okay...
那你也不必去另一座城市
Well, you don't have to leave.
我是說  你可以暫時住在別處
I mean, you could stay someplace else.
艾瑪  這里本就不是我的家
Emma, I don't really live here.
我回來只是為了幫助你們姐妹倆
I only came back to help you and Sutton,
但每一次我的努力  都會讓矛頭
but every single time I do, it always leads
指回我爸身上  而我根本無法打敗他
back to my father, and I can't, I can't beat him.
這讓我很難受
It's killing me.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
知道嗎  真相是
You know what, the truth is,
這里已經沒什么東西屬于我了
there is nothing left for me here anymore.
那我呢
What about me?
抱歉伊森的事沒給你事先報備  但
I'm-I'm sorry I didn't tell you about Ethan, but...
和那件事無關
It's not about that.
跟我走吧
I want you to come with me.
塞爾  我做不到
Uh... uh... Thayer, I can't do that.
梅塞一家是我唯一的家人
The Mercers are the only family I've ever known.
這時候我不能離開他們
I can't leave them right now.
那我也不能
Well, I can't...
我也不能留在這里
I can't stay either.
那就只能告別了
So then that's it?
也許這對大家都好
Maybe it's for the best.
但我
No, I... I...
照顧好自己
Take care of yourself.
你瞧  和新的一樣
See? Good as new.
那我就不在這里礙事了
Guess I'll just get out of your way.
泰德  關于周一那場心理治療
Ted, about that counseling session on Monday.
我決定參加
I'll be there.
那你原有的安排怎么辦
What about your other appointment?
取消了
I cancelled it.
那挺好
That's good to hear,
但我希望你帶著支票薄去  夫人
but I hope you brought your checkbook, ma'am,
因為管道修理賬單可是多得要命
'cause you've rung up quite a hefty plumbing bill.
帕爾馬干酪雞肉片
Chicken parmigiana?
是剩下的
Leftovers.
看來  這里的一切
Looks like everything is getting
正在回歸正軌
back to normal around here.
是的  你爸把下水管道修好了
Yes, your father fixed the drain.
我說的不是管道修理
I wasn't talking about the plumbing.
要我叫蘿倫嗎
Do you want me to get Laurel?
實話說  我真搞不懂你
You know, honestly, I can't figure you out.
前一分鐘  你熱辣無比
One minute, you're hot;
下一分鐘  你就冷若冰霜
the next minute, you're cold.
你到底清不清楚自己想要什么
Do you even know what you want?
那你呢  還跟蹤起我了
What about you? You're practically stalking me.
我根本不感興趣  好嗎
I am not interested, okay?
是嗎
Oh, is that right?
對
Yeah.
我愛夜晚自由的味道
Well, I love the smell of freedom in the evening.
按照你的要求
The press is at the other entrance,
媒體被安排到另一個入口了
just like you requested.
棒極了
Perfect.
這樣有充分時間準備隨后的嘩眾取寵
There'll be plenty of time for grandstanding later.
需要捎你回家嗎
Do you need a lift home?
不用
No.
我中途得去個地方
I've got a stop to make.
告訴我妻子  我這就過去
Tell my wife I'm coming for her.
你當時在旗桿市
You were in Flagstaff?
你該從高爾夫球場打那通電話
You were supposed to make that call from the golf course
這樣才不會招人疑問
so no one would question it.
不用  你什么都不用做
No, I don't want you to do anything.
埃里克隨時會回來
Alec will be here any minute.
我非常清楚怎么搞定他
I know exactly how to handle him.
寶貝  我回來了
Hey, baby, I'm home.
親愛的  我想死你了
Darling, I've missed you so much.
我明白
I'll bet.
莎頓  老天  你真是膽小
Sutton. God, you scare easily.
不然呢  殺人犯已經放出來了
Well, what do you expect? There's a murderer out there.
聽著  塞爾的事我很遺憾
Hey, so, I'm really sorry about the Thayer thing.
真不走運  但愿賭服輸
Tough break, but a deal's a deal.
記得  不許邁出小木屋一步
And if you remember, not one foot outside of the cabin.
我記得  這是你要求的
Your terms, I recall.
要是我不同意呢
And what if I refuse?
你不敢
You wouldn't dare.
試試看
Try me.
該死  擔心的事還是要發生
Shoot. I was afraid this would happen.
我也不會離開這里  所以
See, I'm not going to go either, so...
我們只能告訴家人這個天大的秘密
I think we're gonna just have to tell the family our big secret,
那可就難辦多了  因為我不知道
which is going to be really tough because Kristin,
克里斯汀會有什么反應
I don't really know how she's going to react.
她現在十分脆弱
She's very fragile right now.
你在嚇唬我
You're bluffing.
試試看
Try me.
好
Fine.
我走
I'm leaving,
但泰德和克里斯汀的關系有了很大改善
but Ted and Kristin are making really good progress,
你保證要推動他們
so just promise me that you'll keep pushing them
往正確的方向發展
in the right direction.
我保證  當然  他們可是我爸媽
Yes! Of course! They're my parents.
我怎么會不想讓他們合好
You think I don't want them together?
好吧  日后見
All right, I'll see you in a couple days.
小木屋里我留了幾條干凈的毛巾
I left some clean towels for you at the cabin.
也許你用得到
You may need them.
看見嗎
See,
我也可以很體貼  艾瑪
I can be considerate too, Emma.
地區賽好運
Good luck at Regionals.
我不用碰運氣
I don't need luck.